export const chapter = "Chapter - 2: It's Sweet ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "What is the central theme of the text?",
          optionA: "Victory in conflict",
          optionB: "The joy of life",
          optionC: "Being remembered",
          correctAnswer: "Being remembered",
        },
        {
          question: "According to the text, when is it sweet to be remembered?",
          optionA: "Only in times of peace",
          optionB: "While toiling and struggling in life",
          optionC: "Only when fortune smiles",
          correctAnswer: "While toiling and struggling in life",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does the text suggest about those who whispered in our ear as we toiled and struggled?",
          optionA: "They were absent when we needed them",
          optionB: "They share our happy moments when fortune smiles",
          optionC: "They are always present and supportive",
          correctAnswer: "They share our happy moments when fortune smiles",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What happens when all toils are ended and the conflict is done, according to the text?",
          optionA: "Tumult and strife continue",
          optionB: "Victory is proclaimed, and peace prevails",
          optionC: "Patience and meekness are lost",
          correctAnswer: "Victory is proclaimed, and peace prevails",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In what situations is it sweet to be remembered, as mentioned in the text?",
          optionA: "Only when sailing over the sea",
          optionB: "Wherever we may be",
          optionC: "Only in times of calm and peace",
          correctAnswer: "Wherever we may be",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the text's attitude toward being remembered?",
          optionA: "It is a bitter experience",
          optionB: "It is a source of happiness and comfort",
          optionC: "It is irrelevant to the author",
          correctAnswer: "It is a source of happiness and comfort",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the author's perspective on those who are remembered?",
          optionA: "They should be forgotten",
          optionB: "They are always present in spirit",
          optionC: "They are rarely thought of",
          correctAnswer: "They are always present in spirit",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What must happen before one can await the joy of life, according to the text?",
          optionA: "Struggling and toiling",
          optionB: "The absence of fortune",
          optionC: "The end of patience",
          correctAnswer: "Struggling and toiling",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the ultimate outcome of the conflict in the text?",
          optionA: "Tumult and strife continue indefinitely",
          optionB: "Victory is achieved, and peace is established",
          optionC: "Patience and meekness are lost forever",
          correctAnswer: "Victory is achieved, and peace is established",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "It's sweet to be remembered in the ______________ of this life.",
          optionA: "Chaos",
          optionB: "Turmoil",
          optionC: "Tranquility",
          correctAnswer: "Turmoil",
        },
        {
          question:
            "While toiling up its pathway, and mingling in its ______________.",
          optionA: "Peace",
          optionB: "Happiness",
          optionC: "Strife",
          correctAnswer: "Strife",
        },
        {
          question:
            "While wandering o'er earth's ______________, or sailing o'er its sea.",
          optionA: "Deserts",
          optionB: "Borders",
          optionC: "Valleys",
          correctAnswer: "Borders",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When all our toils are ended, and the conflict all is ______________.",
          optionA: "Ongoing",
          optionB: "Done",
          optionC: "Beginning",
          correctAnswer: "Done",
        },
        {
          question:
            "And peace, in sweetest accents, proclaims the victory ______________.",
          optionA: "Lost",
          optionB: "Achieved",
          optionC: "Unattainable",
          correctAnswer: "Achieved",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When hushed is all the ______________, when calmed is all the strife.",
          optionA: "Laughter",
          optionB: "Tumult",
          optionC: "Celebration",
          correctAnswer: "Tumult",
        },
        {
          question:
            "They who, when not present, in spirit yet were ______________.",
          optionA: "Absent",
          optionB: "Far away",
          optionC: "Near",
          correctAnswer: "Near",
        },
        {
          question:
            "And, as we toiled and struggled, did whisper in our ______________.",
          optionA: "Heart",
          optionB: "Mind",
          optionC: "Ear",
          correctAnswer: "Ear",
        },
        {
          question:
            '"It\'s sweet to be remembered, and thou art not ______________."',
          optionA: "Alone",
          optionB: "Loved",
          optionC: "Forgot",
          correctAnswer: "Forgot",
        },
        {
          question:
            "If fortune smiles upon us, shall share our ______________ lot.",
          optionA: "Unfortunate",
          optionB: "Sad",
          optionC: "Happy",
          correctAnswer: "Happy",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "The central theme of the text is victory in conflict.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Being remembered is a source of happiness and comfort in the text.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The pigeon assured the crow that it would return in a day when flying to the nearest village.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The rabbit entered the hollow in the tree because the pigeon hadn't returned for two days.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When the pigeon returned to the hollow, the rabbit insisted that the hollow was empty.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The cat claimed it couldn't listen properly to their problem because it was uninterested.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The pigeon and the rabbit approached the cat to tell their problem, and the cat listened carefully.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the text, being remembered is sweet only when fortune smiles upon us.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When all toils are ended and the conflict is done, peace proclaims the victory lost.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The rabbit suggested that he and the pigeon should go to the cat to get justice and resolve their dispute.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
